(Penny:)That's why I work at The Cheesecake
Factory. I'm holding out for the right part.
(Leonard:)Alicia, what do you want as your default
setting for DVDs, 5. 1 Dolby or DTS?
(Alicia:)Whatever you think is best, cutie.
[GIGGLES]
Well, DTS has more low-end...
...so okay.
Hey, guys, you will really appreciate this.
I read the best science joke on the Internet.
(Penny:)Alicia, you won't get it,
but it's right up their alley.
(Penny:)Anyway, so this physicist goes
into an ice cream parlor every week...
(Penny:)...orders an ice cream sundae
for himself...
...and offers one to the empty stool
next to him.
This goes on until the owner
asks him what he's doing.
The man says, "Well, I'm a physicist...
(Penny:)...and quantum mechanics teaches us...
(Penny:)...that it is possible
for the matter above this stool...
(Penny:)...to spontaneously turn
into a beautiful woman...
(Penny:)...who might accept my offer
and fall in love."